<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>

<!-- Put site-specific property overrides in this file. -->

<configuration>

<property>
  <name>merge.after.fetch</name>
  <value>false</value>
  <description>If true, then segments of crawl are merged after fetch is complete.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>index.sns</name>
  <value>true</value>
  <description>If true, then the Index-Sns Plugin are index with sns dates. Otherwise, without sns dates.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>plugin.folders</name>
  <value>101tec-nutch-11e55b9/src/plugin,portalu-nutch-gui/src/plugin</value>
  <description>Directories where nutch plugins are located.  Each
  element may be a relative or absolute path.  If absolute, it is used
  as is.  If relative, it is searched for on the classpath.</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>plugin.includes</name>
  <value>admin-.*|protocol-httpclient|urlfilter-regex|parse-(text|html|js|pdf|dummy)|index-(basic|anchor|metadata|sns|more)|query-(basic|site|url|fileformat)|response-(json|xml)|summary-basic|scoring-opic|urlnormalizer-(pass|regex|basic)|crawl-prepare-(dbexport)</value>
  <description>Regular expression naming plugin directory names to
  include.  Any plugin not matching this expression is excluded.
  In any case you need at least include the nutch-extensionpoints plugin. By
  default Nutch includes crawling just HTML and plain text via HTTP,
  and basic indexing and search plugins. In order to use HTTPS please enable 
  protocol-httpclient, but be aware of possible intermittent problems with the 
  underlying commons-httpclient library.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>plugin.excludes</name>
  <value>admin-(search|url-upload)</value>
  <description>Regular expression naming plugin directory names to exclude.  
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>crawl-prepare.order</name>
  <value>de.ingrid.iplug.se.urlmaintenance.UrlmaintenancePreCrawl</value>
  <description>space delimited list of IPreCrawl Implementations to execute these classes in order</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>url.type</name>
  <value>catalog</value>
  <description>catalog or web</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.name</name>
  <value>iplug-se</value>
  <description>HTTP 'User-Agent' request header. MUST NOT be empty - 
  please set this to a single word uniquely related to your organization.

  NOTE: You should also check other related properties:

	http.robots.agents
	http.agent.description
	http.agent.url
	http.agent.email
	http.agent.version

  and set their values appropriately.

  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.description</name>
  <value>PortalU Bot (Nutch)</value>
  <description>Further description of our bot- this text is used in
  the User-Agent header.  It appears in parenthesis after the agent name.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.url</name>
  <value>http://www.portalu.de</value>
  <description>A URL to advertise in the User-Agent header.  This will 
   appear in parenthesis after the agent name. Custom dictates that this
   should be a URL of a page explaining the purpose and behavior of this
   crawler.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.email</name>
  <value>crawler@portalu.de</value>
  <description>An email address to advertise in the HTTP 'From' request
   header and User-Agent header. A good practice is to mangle this
   address (e.g. 'info at example dot com') to avoid spamming.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.version</name>
  <value>Nutch-1.0</value>
  <description>A version string to advertise in the User-Agent 
   header.</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>db.fetch.schedule.class</name>
  <value>org.apache.nutch.crawl.AdaptiveFetchSchedule</value>
  <description>The implementation of fetch schedule. DefaultFetchSchedule simply
  adds the original fetchInterval to the last fetch time, regardless of
  page changes.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.enabled</name>
    <value>false</value>
    <description>If true, sending mail report for each segment is enabled. Otherwise disabled.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.sender.address</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The email-address of the sender of system mails.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.sender.personal</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The personal name of the sender of system mails.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.receiver.address</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The email-address of the default receiver of system mails.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.receiver.personal</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The personal name of the default receiver of system mails.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.host</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The host of the email server.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.port</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The port of the connection with the email server.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.user</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The username for the authentication with the email server.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.password</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>The password for the authentication with the email server.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.auth</name>
    <value>false</value>
    <description>If true, authentification with email server is enabled. Otherwise disabled.</description>
</property>

<property>
    <name>mail.starttls</name>
    <value>false</value>
    <description>If true, starting TLS is enabled. Otherwise disabled.</description>
</property>

<property>
	<name>report.codes</name>
	<value>101,400-417,500-505</value>
	<description>Comma seperated http codes, that will be included into the url report mail. You can also define ranges by seperating two codes with a hyphen.</description>
</property>

</configuration>
